## Pavana NR

## Mobile Application Developer

♥ #1003, D Block, KHB Platinum Apartment, Near Shirke Bus Stop., Bengaluru, 560060, India nr.paavana@gmail.com +91 9886689644

### **Profile**

Hi, I am a programmer, specializing in the mobile app development arena. For the last 4+ years, I have been developing mobile application using Google's Flutter framework. I'm currently employed as mobile application developer at Harita techserv. I'm hands on in all stages of the developing & programming cycle, from planning and design to testing and deployment. No two days are the same for me; my tasks may involve analyzing algorithms, altering code, fixing bugs, brainstorming ideas or integrating new systems. Something that I love about programming is the opportunity to work with people from a wide range of disciplines. The software development life-cycle involves working with so many different people and departments and, as a people person and someone who loves to build new relationships, it's great to be able to come together with other professionals who are striving towards the same goal.

## **Employment History**

May 2021 — Present

## Application Developer at Harita techserv

Bengaluru

- Designed & implemented Provider and GETX Both state management tool to make app more fast & elegant.
- Produced the fully functional mobile applications writing clean code.
- Focus on UI design principles and make apps work intuitively, without compromising on simplicity.
- Have experience with several Firebase services including Firebase Realtime Database, Hosting.
- · Participated with clients in discussion meetings.

Aug 2019 - May 2021

Bengaluru

# Mobile Application Developer at TechInflo Solutions Pvt, Ltd.

- Wrote clean, clear and well-tested code for various projects such as Hello Remotely, Think zone.
- · Unit testing in flutter,
- Developed native applications using Google's Flutter Framework.
- Designed & implemented Bloc a state management tool to make app more fast & elegant.

Aug 2018 — Jul 2019

Mysuru

Junior Software Engineer at Sintheetaa Technologies / Coorgle Consultancy Services(CCS)

#### **Details**

Nationality

Indian

#### Links

pavana-nr-github.io github.com/pavana-nr linkedin.com/in/pavana-nr

#### Skills

Flutter

Firebase

Git

**JSON** 

JIRA

Android Development

#### **Hobbies**

Yoga

- Developed Ionic, Cordova & angular based mobile application to work with web platform using single codebase.
- Worked on 4 versions of an application using different languages like jQuery mobile and angular framework.
- Created various angular directives, controllers, dom, expressions, templates, data binding, etc.
- Creating services for angular controllers for sharing data between multiple controllers to increase code enhancing.
- rest API for various requirements.

#### Education

Jun 2014 – Jul 2016 PES College of Engineering

Mandya M.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering

May 2011 – Jul 2014 GSSS Institute of Engineering and

Mysuru Technology for Women

BE in Information Science and Engineering

#### References

TechInflo Solutions Pvt, Ltd.

Shilpi Gupta

shilpi@techinflo.com +91 9741454762